Number one
K-content channel.
tvN for joy.
Fifteen.
THE FOLLOWING PROGRAM IS
NOT SUITABLE FOR VIEWERS UNDER 15.
VIEWER DISCRETION IS ADVISED.
THIS PROGRAM CONTAINS PRODUCT PLACEMENTS
AND VIRTUAL ADVERTISING.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
PRODUCTION SUPPORTED BY:
MINISTRY OF CULTURE, SPORTS AND TOURISM
KOREA CREATIVE CONTENT AGENCY
THIS DRAMA
IS A WORK OF FICTION
CHILD AND ANIMAL SCENES WERE FILMED SAFELY
UNDER EXPERT SUPERVISION
- D.N.X!
Someone once said
that love is like getting
into an unexpected car accident.
Back then, I had no idea
that I had gotten into a crash
that would take
12 years to recover from.
Reaching out to capture
The paradise in my memory
Following my heartbeat
To find myself
Lost in childhood dreams
I'll go away
Beyond the blue sky
Spreading the wings within me
I will embrace the lost dreams
Another way of mine
At the age of 17
it was his song
that rescued me from my loneliness.
Let's check the final results.
- Please.
- This week's number one is
D.N.X!
DECEMBER WEEK 3 TOP 1
D.N.X
Being a fan gave me friends
when I was lonely.
It helped me find unknown talents.
LET'S GO TO THE CONCERT!
YOU CAN DO IT, DA-REUM
To find myself
- Most of all, I felt alive.
- Lost in childhood dreams
- I was happy.
- I'll go away
Beyond the blue sky
- But to him,
- Spreading the wings within me
- I will embrace the lost dreams
- I'm just another light among many.
- Another way of mine
- D.N.X!
NAM DA-REUM
LEE CHAN, MY NEVER-ENDING STARLIGHT
10 YEARS LATER
TOGETHER FOREVER
ALWAYS ON CHAN'S SIDE
So, I made up my mind
to go to him.
My dream is
to become a successful fan.
SHINING STARLIGHT, LEE CHAN
FOREVER LEE CHAN
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
EPISODE 1
This event will not only be hosting
key VIPs
but major global partners
and the press.
We aim to showcase the future
of Korea's premium fashion market
through world-class partnerships.
And the event will be held
at the S Convention Event Hall.
Well...
Ms. Nam, got something to say?
The venue doesn't have
a waiting room for a large crowd.
I was wondering
how you're planning to handle that...
That's none of your concern.
The operations team
will take care of it.
Just do what you're told to do.
Yes, sir.
That's all.
She's at it again.
She's just too tiring.
Can't she just keep her mouth shut?
She almost caused a headache
for all of us again.
- She's such a nuisance.
- I know.
Goodness.
She's nuts.
SE CORPORATION
SEARCH:
RESIGNATION LETTER
PLEASE TAKE GOOD CARE OF HER
FROM NAM DA-REUM'S MOM
Do you think
my mom will throw a fit
if I tell her I'm quitting?
You were already dead meat
the moment you didn't hand out
these rice cake gifts.
Even a banner is put up at your town
to celebrate your new job.
No.
Chan always stressed
the concept of "unframe,"
which is to "break out of the box."
If I pass tomorrow...
I will
pass, right?
Actually, no.
If I fail, I'll try again.
Whatever happens
I'm going to work at Appello.
But aren't you stepping too far out?
You worked hard
to get into a big company.
I feel like a cog
in the machine there.
Nothing makes my heart race.
What about Appello, then?
It's like a rookie idol group
that just debuted.
Think of how much there is to do.
A company
that could totally transform
if they just utilize someone like me.
Liar.
You're just excited because of Chan.
Either way, look.
Come on and look. Come.
Once I join Appello
I'll become
a fashion marketing legend
and raise them up
into a massive skyscraper.
I'm going to be
their number one employee,
no matter what.
Let's go get accepted!
- Let's go!
YOU HAVE A NEW NOTIFICATION
I'M LISTENING TO THE DEBUT ALBUM
AFTER AGES
YOU GUYS SHOULD CHECK IT OUT TOO!
IN 2015, IDOL GROUP D.N.X DEBUTED
NAM DA-REUM JOINED HER FIRST FANDOM
IN 2017, D.N.X DISBANDED
STILL, SHE DIDN'T LEAVE THE FANDOM
IN 2018, FORMER D.N.X MEMBER LEE CHAN
STARTED FRESH AS AN ACTOR
IN 2019, LEE CHAN LAUNCHED
FASHION BOUTIQUE, APPELLO
IN 2022, LEE CHAN MET HIS GOLDEN ERA
FROM WINNING ROOKIE OF THE YEAR
TO LEADING A FASHION PLATFORM
LEE CHAN IS THE TREND ITSELF
HE'S EVEN CONQUERED FASHION
LOOKING AT HIS CAREER,
HIS SUCCESS IS NO SURPRISE
SHINING STARLIGHT, LEE CHAN
FINE CLOTHES LAST LONG IN YOUR MEMORY
Is he even human?
Just wait.
I'll be there with you soon.
APPELLO ACCEPTANCE ANNOUNCEMENT
AT 2 P.M.
SE CORPORATION
SE CORPORATION AND APPELLO
INVESTMENT AND PARTNERSHIP MEETING
COMPLEMENTARY PARTNERSHIP SYNERGY
How old is their CEO?
From what I hear,
he's only in his early 30s.
- In his early 30s?
- Yes.
Jeez, he's just a kid.
STRATEGIC INVESTMENT
AND PARTNERSHIP PROPOSAL
Let's go, sir.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Kang Ha-gi of Appello.
BUSINESS AND OPERATIONAL MATERIALS
PRELIMINARY DUE DILIGENCE
REQUEST LIST
ADMINISTRATIVE RECORDS
Send us the data, and we'll strongly
consider the investment.
What about the NDA?
We'll be setting up a separate entity
so that's difficult at the moment.
I certainly hope
this new entity isn't
a fashion platform identical to us.
I don't understand.
We're aiming to launch
a fashion platform
that delivers
customized shopping experiences.
Our core strategy is
real-time review-based curation.
FASHION PLATFORM LAUNCHING
The people next door seemed busy
prepping a fashion platform launch.
Customized AI styling.
Real-time review-based curation.
Aren't those the exact concepts
from the files we sent over?
I'm pretty sure
SE Corporation came to look at them
during our due diligence
the other day.
Goodness.
Trends are all similar these days.
If you lead with suspicion,
this negotiation is pointless.
You might be able to copy a trend...
but you can never copy a philosophy.
There's nothing more to discuss.
We're declining your investment.
This industry is smaller
than you think.
If you walk out on us like this
you won't be able
to handle the fallout.
Looks like you failed
to steal our core info.
Why don't you worry about your own
employment contract renewal?
I really can't take it back now.
My resignation went through.
And my belongings are all packed.
Please, Appello.
Please hire me.
1:58 P.M.
OCT. 17, 2025
Gosh, it's 1:59 p.m.
Oh, gosh.
2:00 P.M.
2025 RECRUITMENT
VIEW RESULTS
NAME: NAM DA-REUM
BIRTHDATE: NOVEMBER 27, 1999
LOADING
CONGRATULATIONS, NAM DA-REUM
YOU HAVE BEEN ACCEPTED
IN THE 2025 RECRUITMENT
Oh, my goodness.
I got accepted for real!
Sir, you were so charismatic
back there.
"You can never copy a philosophy."
You know this is no time for jokes.
Run a security check
on our internal files first.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
What's with that woman?
I made it!
Boss, look...
You've got a perfect face print
right on your shirt.
Right here.
Thank you. Farewell!
- You really made it?
- I did.
I'm actually
joining Appello!
- To find myself
- Lost in childhood dreams
- I will go away
- Beyond the blue sky
- Spreading the wings within me
- I will embrace the lost dreams
- Another way of mine
NEIGHBORHOOD
What must it feel like
to be the icon of an era?
Here's the man
who pulled off that monumental feat.
The legend group
who rocked the K-pop scene...
Chan must be busy these days.
He hasn't been showing up at all.
I'm way busier.
Finish up quickly so we can leave.
You've got no empathy at all, do you?
You're all logic and no feelings.
Come on and clock out.
You need to know
when to take a break.
Jeez, you fool.
Fine, let's just go.
To find myself
- No, this is okay. Chan said so.
- Like this?
Hello, sir.
I'm not going. I can't.
This is destiny.
I've found my ideal type.
What should we have?
There you go again.
Excuse me.
Wait.
Done.
I'm letting you take it
since you're a regular.
Thank you so much, sir.
So, your friend lives nearby.
- Who's this?
- How did you get here?
- I took a bus.
- Then on your way back
you can take a chance on me.
Excuse me?
You must be her friend.
- Take a seat. Come on now.
- Okay...
Do you want me to show you
some magic tricks?
Okay.
Let me see this.
No!
This way
it's half-Chan.
No...
Heart-Chan.
Bother-Chan.
The magic
of sticking it back together.
The magic of tearing it apart.
Together, apart, repeat.
Chant his name
Goodbye, my love, Chan
Excuse me.
Chan...
No...
That scared me.
Today would've been a perfect day
if I'd only managed
to have Chan's poster in one piece.
Chan.
It was going pretty well.
What do girls like so much
about that guy, Lee Chan, anyway?
He used to be nothing
but an outcast and a loser.
An outcast and a loser.
"Outcast"?
"Loser"?
There she goes again.
Let's go stop her.
I bet
people can't even imagine his past.
- Was it you?
- Excuse me?
You were the one bullying
and isolating him
weren't you?
I'm never going to forgive you!
Your nose is bleeding.
We're sorry.
We're so sorry.
My friend has been having
such a hard time finding a job
- and life has been so rough
- You did well.
that she ended up developing
anger management issues.
We're truly sorry.
We're so, truly sorry.
What are you apologizing for?
I'm not sorry at all.
Bullying is the worst.
Do you even know what that's like?
I'm sorry.
You don't, do you?
- Jeez.
- What are they doing?
- What the...
- Did he hit her?
My friend is so deeply apologetic
that she's on her knees.
I guess she's reflecting
on her actions a lot, right?
Right?
Well...
That's enough. Just leave.
How generous of you.
Bless you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Bye.
Right?
- Hey, let go of me!
- Knock it off.
What?
She got anger management issues
because she couldn't get a job?
For someone who works at SE.
Do you know her?
She's a stranger.
Exactly.
I should've asked for her number.
Hurry up.
Jeez, wait.
- Throw her.
Oh, man.
It's like
her weight literally doubled
the second she got drunk.
Darn it.
This is nuts.
FOREVER LEE CHAN
Goodness. Anyway,
I guess Da-reum really is
living out the ultimate
successful fan.
I wonder if Chan even knows
that he still has such a die-hard fan
when D.N.X disbanded a decade ago.
Beats me.
Hey, let's go home.
Oh, wait.
Come on, let's go.
SUNGJU STATION
Which department are you in?
I'm with the Merchandising Team.
I'm in Marketing.
Marketing? Me too.
- Really?
- I hope we get along.
My name is Park Young-woo.
What are your names?
My name is Lee Min-a.
- Lee Min-a.
My name is Nam Da-reum.
- Nam Da-reum. Lee Min-a and Da-reum.
- Nam Da-reum.
I see.
Let's get along.
You know they say
loyalty to your batchmates is key.
- How about a fist bump?
- Sure.
You guys became close already?
Congratulations
on joining the Appello family.
I'm Kim Mi-young
the Marketing Team Manager.
I'll be running today's orientation.
Here are your employee ID cards.
- Mr. Young-woo.
- Thank you.
- Ms. Min-a.
And Ms. Da-reum.
Thank you.
Appello currently has 82 employees
plus three new hires joining today.
That means this ID card is basically
Chan's limited-edition merch
with only 85 of them
in the whole world.
It's even customized!
All right, then. Let's dive
into the official company overview.
- Shall we?
- Yes, ma'am.
This way.
- Come this way.
- Yes, ma'am.
They come in different colors...
Ms. Min-a.
Most of Appello's partner brands
are centered online
we host pop-up spaces on floor one
so they can meet customers in person.
It's all right.
We also offer spaces for our brands
such as sewing rooms,
pattern rooms, and studios.
As you can see,
our dress code is completely free.
From tomorrow on, you can wear
a swimsuit, party clothes
or anything that fits your style.
This is the studio
for lookbook and campaign shoots.
All of Appello's visual content is
basically born right here.
NAM DA-REUM
On the fourth floor, we have
Marketing and Merchandising Teams.
Oh, and the CEO's Office.
All right. For our final stop,
let's go meet the CEO.
- What, right now?
- Yes.
Hello, I'm the new hire, Nam Da-reum.
Too cheesy.
Nice to meet you. I'm Nam Da-reum.
"I'm Nam Da-reum."
You sound like a call center agent.
Just act normal.
And don't freeze up in front of Chan.
Here, a secret weapon.
Take this calming pill,
and it will help with your nerves.
The calming pill.
Don't worry about the details.
I will send you the final proposal
by tomorrow morning.
Thank you.
Mr. Kang.
They are our new recruits.
- It's nice to meet you.
- I'm new! I mean I'm Park Young-woo.
It's nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm the new hire, Lee Min-a.
Is that you, Chan?
What the? Why is it someone else?
I'm Nam Da-reum.
NAM DA-REUM
Welcome to Appello.
My door is always open,
so feel free to drop by anytime.
Don't feel too intimidated,
and just treat me as a coworker.
Let's do some great work together.
- Yes, sir.
All right. Shall we wrap up here
and head out?
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
It's Chan.
Ms. Nam.
Ms. Da-reum? What's wrong?
- Are you okay? Try to breathe.
- Ms. Da-reum.
- Please call 911.
- Breathe.
- What is it?
- Is something stuck in her throat?
- You can't breathe?
- What's wrong?
- Goodness.
- Breathe.
Try to breathe.
Da-reum...
Are you okay?
She should be fine now.
I'm not sure
what was choking her, though.
- What...
- What's that?
What is this?
Oh, what's up?
Listen up, everyone.
I've got big news.
Did you guys hear?
A new recruit named Nam Da-reum
made big trouble from day one.
I mean, where is the discipline
in new recruits these days?
What?
Mr. Lee Jin-sang.
Oops.
My mistake.
Go on.
I threw up on Director Lee's pants
at my first company dinner.
Anyone can make a mistake
when they're nervous.
Don't worry about it.
Thank you, Ms. Kim.
Excuse me.
But wasn't Mr. Lee Chan the CEO?
The two were previously co-CEOs
but recently, the system changed
and we now have one CEO.
- Then...
- Director Lee is only in charge
of the fashion
for Appello's key events.
I see.
What was it like
to finally see him in person?
Did you manage to stay composed?
A tear emoji? You must've cried.
Were you that moved?
Let's throw a party
to remember your "made-it" moment.
- What do you want to eat?
- I'm in!
Let's eat
whatever Namda wants to eat today.
- I'm in!
- We're in!
Girls, this is Chan's company
but he's not around.
That's like saying
there are no pads in push-up bras.
That one has 4cm pads.
- It's thick.
- Right. Sure.
I'll take this in all colors.
On top of that
I ended up in our CEO's arms
on my first day.
What?
What kind
of crazy development is this?
I'm done for!
So the one
who slammed her face into your chest
was Ms. Nam Da-reum?
She's from SE Corporation
of all places.
Something doesn't feel right.
If she had put it on her resume,
I wouldn't have hired her.
COMPUTER SKILLS LEVEL 1,
SURVEY ANALYST LEVEL 2...
I don't see a reason
why she wants to work at Appello.
Mr. Kang, do you think
she could be a corporate spy
working with Director Kim?
I looked into it and found out that
he has infiltrated a few businesses
with spies to take them over.
Let's keep
a close eye on her for a while.
In a way, Appello is quite smart.
Everyone is busy
trying to snatch famous designers
but you're going after new ones.
It was Director Lee's idea.
He was sad to see
talented brands disappear
due to their lack of network
in distribution.
Have you two always known each other?
We went to high school together.
Oh, you two must be best friends.
That's why
he left the business with you.
Goodness. I look forward
to working with you.
SE Corporation is now taking part
in the e-commerce industry.
We plan to open up
a fashion platform very soon.
Wait, does that mean
you're competing against Appello?
Compete? Hardly.
We need to be similar in size
for that to happen.
Wouldn't it be weirder
if we fail to lead the market
with our resources
and distribution network?
So you used investment as an excuse
to get our intel, in case you fail.
I heard you've done that
with a few businesses with spies.
Spies?
Then what about Appello?
Do you think one of my people
is there or not?
CEO Kang Ha-gi?
I am Reporter Do Eun-yong
with Insight Business Newspaper.
INSIGHT BUSINESS NEWSPAPER
REPORTER DO EUN-YONG
Nice to meet you. I look forward
to seeing great articles about us.
Why don't you spare me some time?
I have many questions for you.
Please contact my office
to schedule an interview.
I don't mean Appello.
I mean for you.
I'm almost there. See you soon.
I'm sorry. I must be somewhere.
Are you done?
Why are you so dressed up?
You're wearing perfume too.
Stop getting clingy.
Why? It's been so long
since we've met.
You only call me for business.
Why are you staying at a hotel
and not at your place?
Someone kept visiting me.
Be careful.
That can turn into an owner's risk.
We're over already
and it was an industry insider.
You'd better keep that up.
Only date someone
who has something to lose.
I knew it.
That's the CEO Kang Ha-gi I know.
This is why
you haven't dated in a decade...
Never mind. You were unable to date.
You're so cold-hearted.
Find a hobby.
Or start stanning a star.
I already have a bias.
You? Who?
Appello.
I already know.
You like me. Say it's me.
Just say it's me.
Say, "Lee Chan."
Say, "Lee Chan is my bias."
- Appello.
- Lee Chan.
- I'll bite you.
I knew it.
What's with her now?
Let her be.
Hey, Namda!
Come and eat some fried chicken!
No!
I still have a long way to go!
Hey, Mi-mi.
Can I just do
a hundred of these again?
I need to drain myself to forget
what happened at the CEO's office...
It's coming back.
You don't have to mind it.
Things like that happen in life.
It can't.
Guys, how am I going
to face the CEO from now on?
And what about the entire company
thinking I'm a weird woman?
It was only your first day.
If you do your job well
these rumors will die down quickly.
- Do you think so?
- Of course.
And you're just a rookie.
You won't have to meet the CEO often.
Just avoid him.
Right?
I won't have to meet the CEO
at all, right?
- Not at all.
- Not likely.
Right.
Yes, I doubt I'll have to see him.
No, never again.
I'll work hard
and improve my reputation.
As for the CEO...
I'll avoid him.
Yes.
It's our first pop-up store
since TUNZI's launch
so please pay extra attention.
- Yes.
- Yes, ma'am.
TUNZI IS A SPACE
FOR DESIGNER MIN-JI'S...
I'll do it!
Let me help!
I'll take it!
TUNZI OUTFIT SETTING LIST
The doors are closing.
Work hard.
Avoid the CEO.
The doors are closing.
Hello, we're the rookie employees,
Nam Da-reum...
- Park Young-woo...
- And Lee Min-a!
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- How cute.
- I love the energy.
- It's great to meet you.
- Cheers.
- We'll do our best!
Thank you.
- Cheers.
Here comes CEO Kang Ha-gi!
Hello, Mr. Kang!
- Hello, Mr. Kang!
- Hello.
- Mr. Kang, please sit over here.
Goodness, no. Why this table?
Have a seat.
I thought you'd be too busy to come.
I have to leave soon
for a video meeting
with a foreign VC firm.
Mr. Kang, would you like a drink
- I have a video meeting.
- Yes, right.
- Can you pour me one?
- Have some.
Why did the atmosphere turn gloomy?
Everyone! Drink up. Come on.
CEO Ha-gi is with us now
so let's have a drink happily!
Drink up!
- Drink up!
- Mr. Kang.
Right. You aren't drinking.
Please give us your guidance.
We look forward to learning a lot.
Let's call it a day quickly.
Don't let the rookies get too drunk.
Yes, sir.
Let's keep drinking!
Da-reum is at a company dinner,
and I'm really concerned.
She'll chug every single drink
without turning anything down.
She's a born nerd.
That's the problem with Namda.
She tries too hard.
- Oh, wow.
- Manager, please have one.
What? Me?
Gosh, Da-reum. I didn't know
you were capable of this.
I learned it from my friends.
You have great friends.
Wait a second, sweetie.
You need a drink from me.
Of course.
- All right.
- Ms. Nam Da-reum.
Sorry?
Take a drink from me instead.
Right. Yes!
Yes, right. Yes.
Use that glass.
Right. Yes, sir!
Okay.
What?
Team dinners are voluntary.
If you're exhausted, you may go home.
Yes, sir. I will.
MEAT BARBECUE
I should go for a quick recharge.
- Drink up!
- Cheers!
- Have another drink.
I have to be at a meeting soon,
so please excuse me.
Yes, you should get going, Mr. Kang.
Goodbye, Mr. Kang.
Oh, okay.
- I need some more.
- Come on!
Why is Director Kim here?
Darn it.
If I work hard enough
then one day
I'll get to see you in person, right?
Anyway, he looks really good
in this picture.
I must take a picture.
PASSCODE
Why isn't it working?
Zero. Nine. One. Six.
That's Chan's birthday.
Zero. Nine. One...
Ms. Nam.
Yes?
What do you think you're doing here?
Mr. Kang?
Why are you here
in the middle of a company dinner?
What?
Me? You mean me?
Oh, I...
I needed to recharge for a bit.
- Recharge?
- You said you always
welcomed everyone
and that your office
was always open.
So a picture.
I was going to leave
after taking just one picture.
What picture?
A picture...
Now, everyone. Attention, please.
There is one question all rookies
of our company must answer.
Yes, that one.
Now, dear adorable Ms. Lee Min-a
are you on Team Ha-gi or Team Chan?
- What?
- Do you prefer someone like Mr. Kang
who's very trustworthy
and hard on the outside,
but soft on the inside?
Or is it Director Chan
someone unreal,
like he popped out of a fairy tale?
Well, the thing is
there's too much pressure.
If they're too much pressure for you,
you can join Team Jin-sang.
- Join me.
- What?
- Come on. You ruined it.
Hurry up and choose.
In that case, I choose...
Team Ha-gi.
- I knew it.
- I was right.
See? Me too.
- Nice choice, Min-a.
- I was right.
- I had a feeling.
- I'm on Team Ha-gi too!
Why is everyone on Team Ha-gi?
- Is anybody on Team Jin-sang?
- It's Ha-gi.
Did she really break in
because she was just drunk?
Well, Mr. Kang.
I have to stay that was a
very impressive presentation.
Your platform's growth metrics
are outstanding.
And the "Unframe" philosophy?
What a brilliant differentiator
in what is a very crowded market.
Our team will be in touch with you
within the week
to discuss the next steps.
It's a pleasure speaking with you,
Mr. Kang.
Thank you. I hope to see you soon.
You bet. Take care.
She didn't hear that, did she?
Ms. Nam.
Ms. Nam, time to go home.
Wake up, Ms. Nam.
What? Why?
She's driving me insane.
What now?
I must be insane.
I must be.
Yes, I am.
Oh, come on.
I feel like throwing up.
What? You did it with the CEO...
- You slept with him?
- What? No!
I fell asleep in his office.
I knew it. There's no way
our conservative girl would do that.
So why did you go there?
No idea.
I guess
I was in my zombie mode again.
There's a picture of Chan there.
It's not a photoshoot, though.
It's such a candid picture.
You're insane.
You have to do something
about your drunken behavior.
Da-reum,
you literally are killing me.
I'm sorry.
I'll seriously quit drinking now.
Jeez!
Anyway, you didn't do
anything weird in the office, right?
I
hope not.
What is this ominous feeling?
- I don't know.
- Wait, no.
Did you black out?
Yes.
Hey, Da-reum.
- Hello.
- Oh, hello.
Hey, Nam Da-reum!
I saw a new side of you yesterday.
You did something with this thing
and bang, the bottle cap spun around,
flew over there, and blast!
Gosh, you truly are different.
- Give me five.
- What?
M-Me? What did I do? Why...
What's going on?
You were so cool yesterday, Da-reum.
You're the best, Da-reum.
- Good morning.
- Da-reum.
- Yes?
Did you get home safely last night?
You seemed to have left
after getting drunk.
Yes, I did.
He's so good-looking.
Ms. Nam.
Wait, what is this memory?
It feels like Mr. Kang was there.
- Excuse me, Ms. Kim.
- Yes?
By any chance, is Mr. Kang at work?
Mr. Kang?
I think
he spent the night up in his office.
What?
Darn it. What's going on?
What happened?
Why is he looking at me?
Please recall it.
Think hard, Nam Da-reum.
SAMPLE ROOM
I don't think I've sobered up yet.
Da-reum! You were here?
- Do you feel okay?
- Yes.
I got wasted last night, wasn't I?
Did I make any mistakes?
Mistakes? What mistakes?
You left early,
so you didn't have time to do that.
Da-reum, it would've been so much fun
if you stayed until the very end.
At the end of the night,
Director Lee Chan came!
He was so good-looking.
What?
My goodness.
I thought he was just good-looking,
but he was hilarious too.
- Yes.
- See?
He only took a picture with us
to congratulate us on our start here!
My Chan was there?
You should call him
Director Lee at work.
Shouldn't we call him that?
Wait, Da-reum must've been
a fan of D.N.X.
I almost said, "It's Lee Chan!"
It could've been a mistake.
Oh, no.
What's wrong, Da-reum?
Was it something I said?
It's not that.
It's nothing.
Not only was I drunk
but I broke into the CEO's office
and didn't even get to see my Chan.
Why are you even alive, Da-reum?
Just end yourself.
That was my chance
to finally see him in person.
Oh, mother!
Why do you always look for your mom
whenever you see me?
So, about yesterday...
I'm sorry, Mr. Kang.
I remember getting drunk
and walking into your office.
But when I opened my eyes,
it was already morning.
So you don't remember?
How convenient.
You never remember anything.
- Sorry?
- Forget it.
It's better that way.
I wanted to wake you
when you sobered up.
But you were too drunk to do that.
Then what about you?
Well...
I worked and left.
Yes, right? I'm glad.
I'm glad you didn't stay
because of me.
Please be cautious from now on.
That kind of behavior
may cause
an unnecessary misunderstanding.
Yes, sir.
I'm sorry, Mr. Kang.
I won't let
anything like this happen again.
I'm sorry.
- Yes, Ms. Kim.
- Hey, Da-reum.
Go to the showroom on the first floor
and help out with organizing.
Yes, coming.
Ms. Kim needs me at the showroom
so please excuse me.
Ms. Nam.
What? Why is he following me?
The miracle I had always hoped for
did not happen on a special day.
It came into my trivial daily life
in the least expected moment.
MY BIAS, MY BOSS
CHEON SEON-AE
EPILOGUE
Scrub with love
Scrub the dirt off your heart
Every corner, every grime
Let me scrub it off for you
Scrub, scrub with love
The dirt on the bruise of your heart
I will even scrub the bruises
Of your heart with my love
Scrub, scrub
- Oh, my. Mr. Kang.
- Goodness.
I mean,
it's a good morning, Ms. Cheon.
Oh, no.
Did you spend the night up again?
You should take a quick nap.
I'll clean up quickly and leave.
No, it's all right.
My paperwork is all over the place.
That's nothing new.
It's not like
I've ever touched anything.
If you have work to do, go ahead.
I'll make it quick and leave.
Ms. Cheon.
Dear Ms. Cheon.
Would you like
to have a cup of coffee with me?
Coffee? Morning coffee sounds great.
Scrub, scrub, scrub the dirt
- Nice to meet you, Da-reum.
- How do you know my name?
I'm not dreaming, am I?
Overseas training
for outstanding employees?
I feel like she has a hidden agenda.
Mr. Kang.
You look so cool today.
Maybe she's a honey trap
Director Kim sent.
- Call me.
- See you again!
They're dating?
Our company CEO and Chan?
No!
Synced and corrected by
WEISSACHsubs